Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Articles/Congressional Testimonies/Speeches by JG
  - Speeches
    - “A Time to Grow” Commencement Address at Western Kentucky University, Bowling Green, KY – Text, Correspondence, August 5, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 21.)
    - “A Time to Grow” Commencement Address at Western Kentucky University, Bowling Green, KY – Text, Correspondence, Programs, Others, August 5, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 22.)
    - “Television in the Age of the Satellite” Radio and Television News Directors Association – Text, Correspondence, Press Release, October 1, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 23.)
    - NBC Radio Networks Affiliates, New Orleans, Louisiana, October 17, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 24.)
  - Speeches
    - “Television: A Perspective on Tomorrow” Association of National Advertisers, Colorado Springs, Colorado, October 25, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1.)
    - “Television: A Perspective on Tomorrow” Association of National Advertisers, Colorado Springs, Colorado – Related Materials, October 25, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2.)
    - “Communications: The Challenge of Tomorrow” Sigma Delta Chi Convention, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, November 11, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3.)
    - “Communications: The Challenge of Tomorrow” Sigma Delta Chi Convention, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, November 11, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 4.)
    - Speech material (1), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5.)
    - Speech material (2), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6.)
    - Speech material (3), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7.)
    - TV Affiliates Meeting, Hollywood, California – Text and Press Release, March 10, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 8.)
    - “Community and Communications” Baylor University, Waco, Texas – Text and Press Release, April 12, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9.)
    - “Community and Communications” Baylor University, Waco, Texas – Correspondence, April 12, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10.)
    - “Television and the World Community” International Television Contest, West Berlin, Germany – Text, Press Release, Correspondence, August 29, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11.)
    - “Television and the World Community” International Television Contest, West Berlin, Germany – Schedule and Correspondence, August 29, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12.)
  - Speeches
    - “Here to Stay But Not to Stay the Same” Advertisers’ Club of Cincinnati – Text and Correspondence, October 11, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 1.)
    - “Here to Stay But Not to Stay the Same” Advertisers’ Club of Cincinnati – Articles, Press Release, October 11, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 2.)
    - “It’s All Educational Television” William Jewell College, Kansas City, Missouri – Texts, November 9, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 3.)
    - “It’s All Educational Television” William Jewell College, Kansas City, Missouri – Related Materials, November 9, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 4.)
    - Speech Requests, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5.)
    - Speech Material (1), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 6.)
    - Speech Material (2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7.)
    - “Tracking the Future” Soap and Detergent Association, New York, New York – Text and Correspondence, January 26, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 8.)
    - Adcraft Club, Detroit, Michigan – Correspondence, Articles, March 22, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9.)
    - TV Affiliates Convention, New York, New York – Text, Correspondence, Press Release, March 28, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 10.)
    - RCA Personnel Meeting, Buck Hill Falls, Pennsylvania – Draft Outline, Programs, Correspondence, June 13, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 11.)
    - Larchmont Avenue Churchmen, New York, September 15, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12.)
    - WRC 45th Anniversary, Washington, D.C., September 30, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 13.)
    - Radio Affiliates Convention, New York, New York – Text, Correspondence, October 24, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14.)
    - Speech Requests, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15.)
  - Speeches
    - “Event Television” – draft, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1.)
    - “Television Journalism in a Free Society” 11th Annual KMTV Television Public Service Awards Dinner, Omaha, Nebraska, January 27, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2.)
    - “Television Journalism in a Free Society” 11th Annual KMTV Television Public Service Awards Dinner, Omaha, Nebraska - Text, Press Release, Correspondence, January 27, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3.)
    - “Television Journalism in a Free Society” 11th Annual KMTV Television Public Service Awards Dinner, Omaha, Nebraska - Text, Press Release, Correspondence, January 27, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4.)
    - Lindenwood College Symposium, St. Charles, Missouri – Text, Correspondence, February 22, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5.)
    - Security Analysts – Outline and Related Materials, April 18, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6.)
    - “Television and the World of the Seventies” Confederation of British Industry, London, England, April 23, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7.)
    - “Television and the World of the Seventies” Confederation of British Industry, London, England – Correspondence, Schedule, General Information, April 23, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8.)
    - TV Affiliates Meeting, Los Angeles, California – Outline of Remarks, May 13, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9.)
    - NBC Labor Relations Meeting, Princeton, New Jersey – Outline, May 27, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10.)
    - The Anderson School, Larchmont, New York – Commencement Address, June 19, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11.)
    - Heads of Industry Luncheon, United Fund of Allegheny County, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania – Text, Schedule, Press Release, August 12, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12.)
    - Heads of Industry Luncheon, United Fund of Allegheny County, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania – Correspondence, August 12, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13.)
  - Speeches
    - Security Analysts – text and revised draft, October 23, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 1.)
    - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2.)
    - Statements by Julian Goodman, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3.)
    - Speech Requests, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4.)
    - “Creativity, Responsibility, Leadership and Television Society” Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California, January 13, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5.)
    - “Creativity, Responsibility, Leadership and Television Society” Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California - Text, January 13, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6.)
    - January 13, 1970 “Creativity, Responsibility, Leadership and Television Society” Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California - Draft (Box 12, Folder 7.)
    - “Creativity, Responsibility, Leadership and Television Society” Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California - Correspondence and Press Release, January 13, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 8.)
    - “Creativity, Responsibility, Leadership and Television Society” Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California, January 13, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 9.)
    - “The People, The Press, and the First Amendment” University of Texas, Austin – Articles, March 10, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 10.)
    - “The People, The Press, and the First Amendment” University of Texas, Austin - Text, March 10, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 11.)
    - “The People, The Press, and the First Amendment” University of Texas, Austin – Correspondence, March 10, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12.)
    - “The People, The Press, and the First Amendment” University of Texas, Austin – Correspondence, March 10, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 13.)
    - TV Affiliates Meeting, New York – Text and Correspondence, May 21, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14.)
    - “Television’s Silent Majority” Rocky Mountain Association of Broadcasters, Jackson Hole, Wyoming, June 23, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15.)
    - “Television’s Silent Majority” Rocky Mountain Association of Broadcasters, Jackson Hole, Wyoming, June 23, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 16.)
    - “Television’s Silent Majority” Rocky Mountain Association of Broadcasters, Jackson Hole, Wyoming, June 23, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 17.)
  - Speeches
    - Radio Affiliates, San Francisco – Text, Correspondence, and Press Release, October 19, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1.)
    - Glasgow, Kentucky Rotary Club – Correspondence and Press Release, November 5, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2.)
    - “The Future of Television” memo to Station Managers, December 7, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3.)
    - Drafts, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4.)
    - Requests, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5.)
    - Speech material (1), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 6.)
    - Speech material (2), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7.)
    - Speech material (3), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8.)
    - Speech material (4), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9.)
    - Remarks at Broadcast Pioneers’ Mike Award Dinner for WWJ, New York City, February 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10.)
    - “New Pressures on Old Freedoms” Canadian Association of Broadcasters, Montreal, Canada, April 21, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11.)
    - “New Pressures on Old Freedoms” Canadian Association of Broadcasters, Montreal, Canada, April 21, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12.)
    - RTNDA (Radio Television News Directors Association) Communicator, October 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13.)
    - NBC Radio Affiliates Convention, New York – Text, October 27, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 14.)
  - Speeches
    - Requests, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1.)
    - 1971 – (1) (Box 14, Folder 2.)
    - 1971 – (2) (Box 14, Folder 3.)
    - Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California, January 11, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4.)
    - Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California, January 11, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5.)
    - Hollywood Radio and Television Society, Beverly Hills, California -Question and Answers, January 11, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold Medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York – Text of Speech, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold Medal Awarded To Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York – Press Release and Correspondence, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold Medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York – Telegrams, Correspondence, Ad, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11.)
    - “Broadcasting in Wonderland” Gold Medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, International Radio and Television Society, New York – Program Information Packet, March 9, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 12.)
  - Speeches
    - NBC TV Affiliates Convention, Los Angeles, California, May 4, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 1.)
    - NBC TV Affiliates Convention, Los Angeles, California, May 4, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2.)
    - Pre-Convention Meeting, NBC News Personnel, Miami, July 8, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3.)
    - “Fairness Today (Censorship Tomorrow?): Great Issues Forum” University of Southern California, October 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4.)
    - “Fairness Today (Censorship Tomorrow?): Great Issues Forum” University of Southern California, October 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5.)
    - “Fairness Today (Censorship Tomorrow?): Great Issues Forum” University of Southern California, October 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6.)
    - “Fairness Today (Censorship Tomorrow?): Great Issues Forum” University of Southern California, October 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7.)
    - “Fairness Today (Censorship Tomorrow?): Great Issues Forum” University of Southern California, October 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 8.)
    - Cosmopolitan Chamber of Commerce, Chicago, Illinois, December 12, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9.)
    - Cosmopolitan Chamber of Commerce, Chicago, Illinois, December 12, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10.)
    - Requests, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11.)
    - Speech Material, 1972/73 (Box 15, Folder 12.)
    - “Press Freedom Belongs to You” Southern Baptist Radio and Television Commission, Fort Worth, Texas, February 9, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13.)
  - Speeches
    - “Press Freedom Belongs to You” Southern Baptist Radio and Television Commission, Fort Worth, Texas – Text and Correspondence, February 18, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1.)
    - “Press Freedom Belongs to You” Southern Baptist Radio and Television Commission, Fort Worth, Texas, February 18, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2.)
    - NBC TV Affiliates Convention Speech, Los Angeles, California, May 7, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3.)
    - “The Fairness Doctrine vs Press Freedom” American Women in Radio and Television, Miami Beach, Florida, May 18, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4.)
    - “Airwaves, Newsprint, and Press Freedom” Convention of American Women in Radio and Television, Miami Beach, Florida, May 18, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5.)
    - “Airwaves, Newsprint, and Press Freedom” Convention of American Women in Radio and Television, Miami Beach, Florida, May 18, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6.)
    - “Airwaves, Newsprint, and Press Freedom” Commencement Address University of Florida, Gainesville, Florida, August 25, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7.)
    - “What Crossroads?” Association of National Advertisers Workshop on Television Advertising, New York – Text, Press Release, and Correspondence, October 4, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8.)
    - “What Crossroads?” Association of National Advertisers Workshops on Television Advertising, New York – Text, Press Release, and Correspondence, October 4, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9.)
    - Radio and Television News Directors Association, Seattle, Washington – Text and Correspondence, October 12, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10.)
    - Radio and Television News Directors Association, Seattle, Washington – Press Releases and Correspondence, October 12, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11.)
  - Speeches
    - “Television Really is an Education” AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) San Diego, California, November 8, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1.)
    - “Television Really is an Education” Annual Meeting of the AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) San Diego, California, November 8, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2.)
    - “Television Really is an Education” AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) San Diego, California, November 8, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3.)
    - Central Presbyterian Church of Denver, Colorado, Significant Speakers Series – Schedule, Text, Press Releases, Correspondence, December 12, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4.)
    - Requests, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5.)
    - NBC TV Affiliates Convention, May 21, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 6.)
    - “What Good is Freedom of the Press if There Isn’t One” APBA (Associated Press Broadcasters Association) Kansas City, Missouri, May 31, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7.)
    - “What Good is Freedom of the Press if There Isn’t One” APBA (Associated Press Broadcasters Association) Kansas City, Missouri, May 31, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8.)
    - “What Good is Freedom of the Press if There Isn’t One” APBA (Associated Press Broadcasters Association) Kansas City, Missouri, May 31, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9.)
    - RCA Laboratories, Princeton, New Jersey, June 11, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10.)
    - ABU (Asian Broadcasting Union) Tokyo, Japan, October 7, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11.)
    - ABU (Asian Broadcasting Union) Tokyo, Japan, October 7, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12.)
    - ABU (Asian Broadcasting Union) Tokyo, Japan, October 7, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13.)
  - Speeches
    - World Communications Meeting, Acapulco, Mexico, October 25, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1.)
    - World Communications Meeting, Acapulco, Mexico, October 25, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2.)
    - UN Association of New York Award Dinner Honoring Pauline Frederick, October 30, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3.)
    - Harvard Business School, Cambridge, Massachusetts, December 5, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4.)
    - General Requests, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5.)
    - Requests, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6.)
    - Speech Material (1), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7.)
    - Speech Material (2), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8.)
    - Speech Material (3), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9.)
    - Speech Material (4), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10.)
    - Speech Material (5), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11.)
    - Speech Material (6), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12.)
    - Speech Material (7), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13.)
    - “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” National conference of Christians and Jews, Memphis, Tennessee, April 28, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14.)
    - “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” National conference of Christians and Jews, Memphis, Tennessee, April 28, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15.)
    - “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” National conference of Christians and Jews, Memphis, Tennessee – Text, Correspondence, and Press Release, April 28, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 16.)
    - “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” National conference of Christians and Jews, Memphis, Tennessee “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” – Text and Tape Recording, April 28, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 17.)
    - “The Public Interest vs. Special Interest” National conference of Christians and Jews, Memphis, Tennessee – Text, Correspondence, and Press Release, April 28, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 18.)
  - Speeches
    - TV Affiliates, Los Angeles, California – Notes, May 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1.)
    - Kentucky Broadcasters Association, Bowling Green, Kentucky, October 23, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2.)
    - Lazard Freres Group Dinner, Links Club, New York, December 3, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3.)
    - “Freedom: The First Priority” Anti Defamation League Dinner, Atlanta, Georgia, December 6, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4.)
    - “Freedom: The First Priority” Anti Defamation League Dinner, Atlanta, Georgia, December 6, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5.)
    - “Freedom: The First Priority” Anti Defamation League Dinner, Atlanta, Georgia, December 6, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6.)
    - Requests, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7.)
    - General, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8.)
    - Speech Material – 1. Eisenhower – Committee on National purpose; 2. Harris Poll - Medicine College, TV News, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 14.)
    - Speech Material, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15.)
    - George Washington University Law Alumni, January 30, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16.)
    - “Freedom from Restriction – A Franchise for All” International Franchise Association, Palm Springs, California, February 10, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17.)
  - Speeches
    - “Freedom from Restriction – A Franchise for All” International Franchise Association, Palm Springs, California– Correspondence and Press Release, February 10, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1.)
    - “Freedom from Restriction – A Franchise for All” International Franchise Association, Palm Springs, California – Correspondence and Press Release, February 10, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2.)
    - “A Broadcaster’s Declaration of Independence” NAB Convention (National Association of Broadcasters) Chicago, Illinois, March 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3.)
    - “A Broadcaster’s Declaration of Independence” NAB Convention (National Association of Broadcasters) Chicago, Illinois, March 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4.)
    - “A Broadcaster’s Declaration of Independence” NAB Convention (National Association of Broadcasters) Chicago, Illinois, March 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5.)
    - Ithaca College, NY – Photographs?, October 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6.)
    - Ithaca College, NY, October 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7.)
    - Ithaca College, NY, October 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8.)
    - Overseas Press Club, NY, November 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 9.)
    - Requests, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10.)
    - Requests, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11.)
    - Speech Material (1), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 12.)
    - Speech Material (2), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13.)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Glasgow, Kentucky, January 31, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14.)
    - March 25, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15.)
    - University Club Speech, Physicians Scientific Society, NY, April 4, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16.)
  - Speeches
    - University Club Speech, Physicians Scientific Society, NY, April 4, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters, Hilton Head, South Carolina, July 11, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters, Hilton Head, South Carolina, July 11, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters, Hilton Head, South Carolina – Correspondence and Press Release, July 11, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters, Hilton Head, South Carolina – Text, July 11, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5.)
    - RTNDA Convention (Radio Television News Directors Association) San Francisco, CA, September 17, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6.)
    - RTNDA Convention (Radio Television News Directors Association) San Francisco, CA, September 17, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7.)
    - RTNDA Convention (Radio Television News Directors Association) San Francisco, CA, September 17, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8.)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, NY, November 9, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9.)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, NY, November 9, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10.)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, NY, November 9, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11.)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation, NY, November 9, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12.)
  - Speeches
    - KING TV 50th Anniversary Luncheon, Spokane, Washington, December 15, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1.)
    - KING TV 50th Anniversary Luncheon, Spokane, Washington, December 15, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2.)
    - KING TV 50th Anniversary Luncheon, Spokane, Washington, December 15, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 3.)
    - Requests, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 4.)
    - Speech Material, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5.)
    - Speech Material, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6.)
    - Speech Material, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7.)
    - Speech Material, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8.)
    - “The Power and Responsibilities of Television” Harvard Business School Regional Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, March 10, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9.)
    - “The Power and Responsibilities of Television” Harvard Business School Regional Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, March 10, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10.)
    - “The Power and Responsibilities of Television” Harvard Business School Regional Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, March 10, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 11.)
    - “The Power and Responsibilities of Television” Harvard Business School Regional Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, March 10, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 12.)
    - WWLP 25th Anniversary Springfield Television Corporation, Massachusetts, March 17, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 13.)
    - WWLP 25th Anniversary Springfield Television Corporation, Massachusetts, March 17, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 14.)
    - WWLP 25th Anniversary Springfield Television Corporation, Massachusetts – Text and Press Release, March 17, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 15.)
    - Young Presidents Association, Fort Worth, Texas, March 30, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 16.)
    - Young Presidents Association, Fort Worth, Texas, March 30, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 17.)
    - Young Presidents Association, Fort Worth, Texas, March 30, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 18.)
  - Speeches
    - Young Presidents Association, Fort Worth, Texas, March 30, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1.)
    - Young Presidents Association, Fort Worth, Texas, March 30, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2.)
    - Federal Communications Bar Association Luncheon, Washington DC, May 17, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 3.)
    - Federal Communications Bar Association Luncheon, Washington DC, May 17, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4.)
    - Federal Communications Bar Association Luncheon, Washington DC, May 17, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5.)
    - Federal Communications Bar Association Luncheon, Washington DC, May 17, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6.)
    - Closed Circuit Telecast NBC Top Management, September 20, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 7.)
    - B’nai B’rith Award to J. Harris, Annual Banquet, Houston, Texas, September 28, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8.)
    - B’nai B’rith Award to J. Harris, Annual Banquet, Houston, Texas, September 28, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9.)